Mt. Pleasant Neighbors Association/Historic Mt. Pleasant
DC Public Library, Special Collections
Mt. Pleasant Neighbors Association/Historic Mt. Pleasant Records
1959-1964; 1985-1996
DC Public Library, Special Collections
0.6 linear feet; 2 boxes
037
Detailed Description of the Collection
- Series 1
  - Mount Pleasant Neighbors Association - Clean-Up Program and Brochures, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Mount Pleasant Neighbors Association - Clean-Up Program and Brochures, Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Mount Pleasant Neighbors Association - Clean-Up Program and Brochures, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Mount Pleasant Neighbors Association - Clippings, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Mount Pleasant Neighbors Association - Correspondence to the Neighborhood Association, 1959-1964 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Mount Pleasant Neighbors Association - Day Care for Children of Working Mothers, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Mount Pleasant Neighbors Association - Drafts of Letters, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Mount Pleasant Neighbors Association - Forms and Stationery, Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Mount Pleasant Neighbors Association - Map of Mount Pleasant, Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Mount Pleasant Neighbors Association - Meeting Announcements, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Mount Pleasant Neighbors Association - Meeting Sign-In Sheet, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Mount Pleasant Neighbors Association - Membership Information, Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Mount Pleasant Neighbors Association - Minutes of Meetings, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Mount Pleasant Neighbors Association - Mount Pleasant Artists, Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Mount Pleasant Neighbors Association - Neighborhood Association Correspondence, 1959-1964 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Mount Pleasant Neighbors Association - Nomination of Committee Officers, Undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Mount Pleasant Neighbors Association - Proposal to endorse day care funding for children of working mothers, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Mount Pleasant Neighbors Association - Resolution opposing construction of the “Cross Park Freeway” 1959, Undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Mount Pleasant Neighbors Association - Resolution to develop recreational program, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Mount Pleasant Neighbors Association - Street Car and transportation change-over, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Mount Pleasant Neighbors Association - Street Car and transportation change-over, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Mount Pleasant Neighbors Association - Street Car and transportation change-over, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Mount Pleasant Neighbors Association - Street Car and transportation change-over, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Mount Pleasant Neighbors Association - Testimony regarding Home Rule, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Historic Mount Pleasant - Application for the creation of a Mount Pleasant Historic District, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Historic Mount Pleasant - Guidelines for Building Permits in the Historic District, Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Historic Mount Pleasant - Membership Information, 1985, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Historic Mount Pleasant - Preservation Briefs, Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Historic Mount Pleasant - Results of Mount Pleasant Planning Workshop, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Historic Mount Pleasant - Revolving Loan Fund, Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)